Inventory of the Michael McFaul Collection
Hoover Institution Archives
Michael McFaul collection
1989-2002
94039
Hoover Institution Archives
48 manuscript boxes, 18 oversize boxes, 6 card file boxes (33.8 linear feet)
The collection contains materials related to political and economic conditions in the Soviet Union and post-Soviet Russia, consisting of printed matter, sound and video recordings of interviews of Russian political leaders, and miscellany. Mainly used as research material for the book by Michael McFaul and Sergei Markov, The Troubled Birth of Russian Democracy: Parties, Personalities, and Programs (Stanford, 1993).
McFaul, Michael, 1963-, collector
Access
Collection is open for research.
The Hoover Institution Archives only allows access to copies of audiovisual items. To listen to sound recordings or to view videos or films during your visit, please contact the Archives at least two working days before your arrival. We will then advise you of the accessibility of the material you wish to see or hear. Please note that not all audiovisual material is immediately accessible.
Acquisition Information
Materials were acquired by the Hoover Institution Archives in 1994 with an additional increment in 2002.
Accruals
Materials may have been added to the collection since this finding aid was prepared. To determine if this has occurred, find the collection in Stanford University's online catalog at http://searchworks.stanford.edu/. Materials have been added to the collection if the number of boxes listed in the online catalog is larger than the number of boxes listed in this finding aid.
Related Materials
Dmitriĭ Aleksandrovich Levchik papers, Hoover Institution Archives
Soviet and post-Soviet independent publications collection, Hoover Institution Archives
Levinskaia-Lesman collection, Hoover Institution Archives
Demokraticheskaia Rossiia records, Hoover Institution Archives
Sergeĭ Somov papers, Hoover Institution Archives
Marietta Omarovna Chudakova papers, Hoover Institution Archives
Biographical Note
Michael McFaul was born and raised in Montana. He received his BA in international relations and Slavic languages and his MA in Soviet and East European studies from Stanford University in 1986. He was awarded a Rhodes scholarship to Oxford, where he completed his PhD in international relations in 1991.
McFaul served as deputy director at the Freeman Spogli Institute and director of the Center on Democracy, Development, and Rule of Law at Stanford University. He is the Peter and Helen Bing Senior Fellow at the Hoover Institution and a professor of political science at Stanford University. He was also a nonresident senior associate at the Carnegie Endowment for International Peace.
From 2009 to 2012 Michael McFaul served as the special assistant to the president and senior director for Russia and Eurasian affairs at the National Security Council, and on January 10, 2012, McFaul was sworn in as the United States ambassador to the Russian Federation.
McFaul is the author and editor of many monographs on political and economic conditions in the USSR and post-Soviet Russia. His articles have appeared in Constitutional Political Economy, Foreign Affairs, Foreign Policy, International Organization, International Security, Journal of Democracy, Political Science Quarterly, Post-Soviet Affairs, and World Politics.
Scope and Content of Collection
The collection consists largely of material collected and created by Michael McFaul over the course of research on topics related to political and economic conditions in the Soviet Union and post-Soviet Russia, and especially to the parliamentary and presidential election campaigns of 1993 to 1999 and Soviet defense industry conversion. It is comprised of sound and video recordings of interviews of Russian political leaders, printed matter, and miscellany.
The Sound Recordings include unique oral history interviews of Russian leaders and statesmen, contemporary politicians, scientists and scholars, as well as survey research conducted by Michael McFaul in Russia in 1991 to 2002, related to political, economic, and social conditions in the Soviet Union and post-Soviet Russia. The sound recordings were arranged by McFaul in two groups: first by a numbered segment created in 1991 to 1993, then alphabetically by speaker or organization name.
Video recordings consist of episodes of U.S. television programs and survey research in Russia on federalism, political parties, and elections. Materials arranged chronologically by date of broadcast. The titles are taken from cassette labels.
The Subject File contains collected research material relating to political issues in Russia. Materials include reports, memoranda, lists, notes, clippings, pamphlets, reprints, leaflets, and election campaign literature, arranged alphabetically by subject.
The Printed Matter series consists of Russian newspapers, journals, and brochures ranging across the political spectrum, arranged in two groups by format.
Markov, Sergeĭ, 1958-; Audiotapes.; Russia (Federation)--Economic conditions--1991-; Russia (Federation)--Politics and government--1991-; Soviet Union--Economic conditions--1985-1991.; Soviet Union--Politics and government--1985-1991.
- Sound recordings, 1991-2002 (Box 1-5)
  - Oral history interviews of Russian political leaders, 1991-1993 (Box 1-2, Tape 1-62)
    Scope and Contents note
    Compact sound cassettes retain the original numbers.
    - Aksiuchits, Viktor, co-chair of the Russian Christian Democratic Movement, 29 May 1991 (Box 1)
      Access
      Use copy reference number: 94039_a_0008335
    - Alksnis, Viktor, former co-chair of the Soiuz, 15 February 1991 (Box 1)
      Use copy reference number: 94039_a_0008336
    - Chubaĭs, Igor, co-founder of the Democratic Platform, 06 June 1991 (Box 1)
      Use copy reference number: 94039_a_0008339
    - Dmitriev, Viktor, co-chair of the Democratic Party of Russia, 02 June 1991 (Box 1)
      Use copy reference number: 94039_a_0008340
    - Frolov, Ivan, member of the Communist Party of Soviet Union (CPSU) Politburo, former editor of Pravda, 15 April 1993 (Box 1)
      Use copy reference number: 94039_a_0008343
    - Gdlian, Tel'man, USSR People's Deputy, founder of the New Russia, 14 June 1991 (Box 1)
      Use copy reference number: 94039_a_0008344
    - Korovikov, Igor, Chairman of the Party for Free Labor, 30 April 1991 (Box 1)
      Use copy reference number: 94039_a_0008350
    - Kosolapov, Richard, founder of the United Workers' Front; Dmitriĭ Vasil'ev, founder of the Pamiat' society, 29 May 1991-06 June 1991 (Box 1)
      Use copy reference number: 94039_a_0008351
    - Kuzin, Viktor, and Boxer, Blahumup, 20 May 1991-23 May 1991 (Box 1)
      Use copy reference number: 94039_a_0008354
      Side A label reads: Boxer, Bla[?]umup, 5-20-91
      Side B label reads: Kusin, May 23, 91 3
    - Kuzin, Viktor, and Lumupkob, Yuri, 23 May 1991 (Box 1)
      Use copy reference number: 94039_a_0008353
      Part 1: Yuri Lumupkob - Christ Demo Union 5-23-91
      Part 2: Kusin, May 23, 91 2
    - Kuzin, Viktor, co-founder of the Democratic Union, 22 May 1991-23 May 1991 (Box 1)
      Use copy reference number: 94039_a_0008352
    - Lukianov, Anatoliĭ, member of the CPSU Politburo, Speaker of the USSR Congress of People's Deputies, leader of the August 1991 putsch, 02 November 1993 (Box 1)
      Use copy reference number: 94039_a_0008361
    - Lukianov, Anatoliĭ, member of the CPSU Politburo, Speaker of the USSR Congress of People's Deputies, leader of the August 1991 putsch, 05 November 1993 (Box 1)
      Use copy reference number: 94039_a_0008363
      Lukianov, Anatoliĭ, CPSU Politburo member, Speaker of USSR Congress of People's Deputies, leader of August 1991 putsch
    - Lunin, Valeriĭ, leader of the Republican Party, Democratic Platform, 14 April 1991 (Box 1)
      Use copy reference number: 94039_a_0008355
    - Lysenko, Vladimir, co-chair of the Democratic Platform of the Republican Party, and the Democratic Congress, 14 June 1991 (Box 1)
      Use copy reference number: 94039_a_0008365
    - Lyzlov, Viacheslav, former leader of the Democratic Party, 02 February 1991 (Box 1)
      Use copy reference number: 94039_a_0008368
    - Maliutin, Mikhail, founder of the Moscow People's Front, 25 May 1991 (Box 1, Box 2)
      Use copy reference number: 94039_a_0008369
    - Malykhin, Anatoliĭ, and Zolotarev, Viktor, 27 May 1991-28 May 1991 (Box 1)
      Use copy reference number: 94039_a_0008372
      Part 1: Malykhin, Anatoliĭ, leader of Kuzbass Strike Committees, 1991 May 27
      Part 2: Viktor Zolotarev, Chairman of Cadet Party, 1991 May 28
    - Medvedev, Anatoliĭ, co-founder of the Moscow Popular Front, Russian Republic People's Deputy, 16 April 1991-04 June 1991 (Box 1)
      Use copy reference number: 94039_a_0008376
      Parts 1-3:
      Medvedev, Anatoliĭ, co-founder Moscow Popular Front, Russian Republic People's Deputy, 1991 April 16
      Part 4:
      Ponomarev, Lev, Co-Chair Democratic Russia, 1991 June 4
    - Meeting of Steering Committee, Independent Miner's Union, 08 June 1991 (Box 1)
      Use copy reference number: 94039_a_0008377
    - Ogorodnikov, Aleksandr, Chairman of the Christian Democratic Union, 24 May 1991 (Box 1)
      Use copy reference number: 94039_a_0008378
      Ogorodnikov, Aleksandr, Chairman of Christian Democratic Union, 1991 May 24
    - Prokhanov, Aleksandr, editor of Den', leader of the National Salvation Front, 27 October 1993 (Box 1)
      Use copy reference number: 94039_a_0008381
    - Rakitskaia, Galina, labor activist, senior figure in the Social Democratic Party of Russia, 28 May 1991 (Box 1)
      Use copy reference number: 94039_a_0008382
    - Rumiantsev, Oleg, co-chair of the Social Democratic Party; Chairman of the Russian Constitutional Commission, 31 May 1991 (Box 1)
      Use copy reference number: 94039_a_0008538
    - Ryzhkov, Nikolaĭ, former Soviet Prime Minister and member of the CPSU Politburo, 30 September 1992 (Box 1)
      Use copy reference number: 94039_a_0008546
    - Maliutin, Mikhail, founder of the Moscow People's Front, 25 May 1991 (Box 1, Box 2)
    - Ryzhkov, Nikolaĭ, former Soviet Prime Minister and member of the CPSU Politburo, 25 August 1992 (Box 2)
      Use copy reference number: 94039_a_0008550
    - Ryzhkov, Nikolaĭ, former Soviet Prime Minister and member of the CPSU Politburo, 11 August 1992 (Box 2)
      Use copy reference number: 94039_a_0008551
    - Schneĭder, Mikhail, 1991 May 1 (contd.). Boris Kagarlitskiĭ, leader of the Socialist Party, 06 April 1991-01 May 1991 (Box 2)
      Use copy reference number: 94039_a_0008773
      Parts 1, 3-4: Schneider
      Part 2: Kagarlitskiĭ
    - Schneĭder, Mikhail, Coordinating Council of the Democratic Russia, 17 April 1991-19 April 1991 (Box 2)
      Use copy reference number: 94039_a_0008553
    - Schneĭder, Mikhail, Coordinating Council of the Democratic Russia, 19 April 1991 (Box 2)
      Use copy reference number: 94039_a_0008554
    - Sedykh-Bondarenko, Iuriĭ, Deputy Chairman of the Moscow City Council, 23 May 1991 (Box 2)
      Use copy reference number: 94039_a_0008556
    - Shablinskiĭ, Il'ia, Secretary of the Federation of labor, 26 May 1991 (Box 2)
      Use copy reference number: 94039_a_0008557
    - Shemaev, Lev, leader of the Democratic Russia, 22 May 1991 (Box 2)
      Use copy reference number: 94039_a_0008561
    - Shmirkov, Iuriĭ, Coordinating Council of the Christian Democratic Union, 23 May 1991 (Box 2)
      Use copy reference number: 94039_a_0008562
    - Shostakovskiĭ, Viacheslav, co-chair of the Movement for Democratic reform; co-chair of the Republican Party of Russia, 17 April 1991 (Box 2)
      Use copy reference number: 94039_a_0008567
    - Skubko, Iuriĭ, co-founder of the Democratic Union, 02 March 1991 (Box 2)
      Use copy reference number: 94039_a_0008568
    - Skubko, Iuriĭ, co-founder of the Democratic Union (Box 2)
      Use copy reference number: 94039_a_0008570
      Skubko recalls his work with the Social Democrats.
    - Sungurov, Aleksandr, Chair of the St. Petersburg Democratic Party, 05 May 1991 (Box 2)
      Use copy reference number: 94039_a_0008659
    - Terekhov, Aleksandr, former Deputy Chairman of the Democratic Party, 26 June 1991 (Box 2)
      Use copy reference number: 94039_a_0008660
    - Travkin, Nikolaĭ, Chair of the Russian Democratic Party, 13 June 1991 (Box 2)
      Use copy reference number: 94039_a_0008663
    - Ul'ianovskiĭ, Rostislav, former head of the Third World Section of the International Department of the Central Committee of the CPSU, 07 March 1991 (Box 2)
      Use copy reference number: 94039_a_0008665
    - Vasileev, Dmitriĭ, leader of Pamiat', 04 June 1991 (Box 2)
      Use copy reference number: 94039_a_0008667
    - Yanaev, Evgeniĭ, Soviet Vice-President, member of the CPSU Politburo, leader of the August 1991 putsch, 28 October 1993 (Box 2)
      Use copy reference number: 94039_a_0008671
    - Yeltsin, Boris, address to Democratic Russia during Presidential campaign, 01 June 1991 (Box 2)
      Use copy reference number: 94039_a_0008669
    - Zamiatin, Leonid, member of the CPSU Central Committee, 06 November 1993 (Box 2)
      Use copy reference number: 94039_a_0008676
  - Interviews of Russian political leaders and survey research groups' recordings, 1991-2002 (Box 3-5, Tape 63-170)
    Compact sound cassettes arranged alphabetically by speaker or organization name, according to the labels.
    - Akimov, Vladimir, 02 August 1995 (Box 3)
      Use copy reference number: 94039_a_0008677
    - Akimov, Vladimir (Box 3)
      Use copy reference number: 94039_a_0008688
    - Aksiuchits, Viktor, co-chair of the Russian Christian Democratic Movement, 07 June 1995 (Box 3)
      Use copy reference number: 94039_a_0008680
    - Alksnis, Viktor Imantovich (Box 3)
      Use copy reference number: 94039_a_0008266
    - 'Almas' (Box 3)
      Use copy reference number: 94039_a_0006674
      Throughout the program, the audio has speed issues. Likely, the original recorder was malfunctioning.
    - Arbatov, Alekseĭ, 16 May 1995 (Box 3)
      Use copy reference number: 94039_a_0008684
    - Armenian Republican Party, 22 May 1991 (Box 3)
      Use copy reference number: 94039_a_0008685
    - Boldyrev, IUriĭ, 15 May 1995 (Box 3)
      Use copy reference number: 94039_a_0006682
    - Boxer, Vladiimir, Coordinating Council of the Democratic Russia, 27 May 1995 (Box 3)
      Use copy reference number: 94039_a_0008756
    - Boxer, Vladiimir, Coordinating Council of the Democratic Russia (Box 3)
      Use copy reference number: 94039_a_0008758
    - Boxer, Vladiimir, Coordinating Council of the Democratic Russia, 13 May 1995 (Box 3)
      Use copy reference number: 94039_a_0008759
    - Burbulis, Gennadiĭ, 30 June 1995 (Box 3)
      Use copy reference number: 94039_a_0008762
    - Byzov, Leontiĭ (Box 3)
      Use copy reference number: 94039_a_0008763
    - Central Aerohydrodynamic Institute (TsAGI) commercial director (Box 3)
      Use copy reference number: 94039_a_0006676
    - Centrist Blok, undated, and Popov press conference, 13 February 1991 (Box 3)
      Use copy reference number: 94039_a_0008764
    - Chester Crocker on American policies in Southern Africa, 31 March 1990 (Box 3)
      Use copy reference number: 94039_a_0008267
      This is a recording of an event where in attendance were Michael McFaul and Chester Crocker. The subject of this event is American foreign policy as it pertains to South Africa and Cubans in Angola.
    - Demokraticheskaia Rossiia, 14 July 1992 (Box 3)
      Use copy reference number: 94039_a_0008765
    - Dianov, Maksim, 30 May 1995 (Box 3)
      Use copy reference number: 94039_a_0008768
    - Dubov, Igor (Box 3)
      Use copy reference number: 94039_a_0008769
    - Ferrite Domen Co, 31 July 1992 (Box 3)
      Use copy reference number: 94039_a_0006667
    - Filatov, Sergeĭ, 25 March 1998 (Box 3)
      Use copy reference number: 94039_a_0008770
      This recording is effectively blank. The cassette features the sounds on a tape being recorded, but fed zero signal, on side A. Side B is blank.
    - Focus group discussions on Russian federalism, political parties, and elections, Moscow, Galich, and Tambov, Russia (Box 3)
      Use copy reference number: 94039_a_0005503
    - Focus group discussions on Russian federalism, political parties, and elections, Moscow, Galich, and Tambov, Russia (Box 3)
      Use copy reference number: 94039_a_0005506
    - Focus group discussions on Russian federalism, political parties, and elections, Moscow, Galich, and Tambov, Russia (Box 3)
      Use copy reference number: 94039_a_0005509
    - Focus group discussions on Russian federalism, political parties, and elections, Moscow, Galich, and Tambov, Russia, 12 December 1999 (Box 3)
      Use copy reference number: 94039_a_0005514
      Part 1: 11:00
      Part 2: 15:00
    - Focus group discussions on Russian federalism, political parties, and elections, Moscow, Galich, and Tambov, Russia, 13 January 2000 (Box 3)
      Use copy reference number: 94039_a_0008317
    - Focus group discussions on Russian federalism, political parties, and elections, Moscow, Galich, and Tambov, Russia, 14 January 2000 (Box 3)
      Use copy reference number: 94039_a_0008318
    - Focus group discussions on Russian federalism, political parties, and elections, Moscow, Galich, and Tambov, Russia, 30 November 1999 (Box 3)
      Use copy reference number: 94039_a_0008320
    - Focus group discussions on Russian federalism, political parties, and elections, Moscow, Galich, and Tambov, Russia, 03 April 2000 (Box 3)
      Use copy reference number: 94039_a_0008321
    - Focus group discussions on Russian federalism, political parties, and elections, Moscow, Galich, and Tambov, Russia, 04 April 2000 (Box 3)
      Use copy reference number: 94039_a_0008322
    - Gaĭdar, Yegor, 04 July 1992 (Box 4)
      Use copy reference number: 94039_a_0008774
    - Golov, Anatoliĭ, Chair of the St. Petersburg Social Democratic Party, 23 June 1995 (Box 4)
      Use copy reference number: 94039_a_0008775
    - Gozman, Leonid, 17 July 1995 (Box 4)
      Use copy reference number: 94039_a_0008776
    - Grazhdanskiĭ Soiuz, 21 June 1992 (Box 4)
      Use copy reference number: 94039_a_0006680
      Part 1: Civic Union 6/21/92
      Part 2: Grazhgah[???] [???] 6/21?/92
    - Igrunov, Viacheslav, 26 July 1995 (Box 4)
      Use copy reference number: 94039_a_0008777
    - Impuls sound recording from 5 Mar 1993 and Yaru sound recording from 10 Mar 1993, 05 March 1993-10 March 1993 (Box 4)
      Use copy reference number: 94039_a_0006664
      Sleeve spine label reads: A YARU 10.03.93 / B Impuls 05.03.93
    - 'Impuls,' NPO (nauchno-proizvodstvennoe ob"edinenie) (Box 4)
      Use copy reference number: 94039_a_0006662
    - 'Impuls,' NPO (nauchno-proizvodstvennoe ob"edinenie) (Box 4)
      Use copy reference number: 94039_a_0006672
    - Khakamada, Irina, 26 August 1995 (Box 4)
      Use copy reference number: 94039_a_0008779
    - Kharichev, Igor, co-founder of the Democratic Congress and aide to Sergeĭ Stankevich, 22 June 1995 (Box 4)
      Use copy reference number: 94039_a_0008780
    - Khasbulatov, Ruslan, 07 June 1995 (Box 4)
      Use copy reference number: 94039_a_0008781
    - Khomiakov, Valeriĭ, 22 June 1995 (Box 4)
      Use copy reference number: 94039_a_0008782
    - Khramov, Sergeĭ, 02 August 1995 (Box 4)
      Use copy reference number: 94039_a_0008785
    - Khrunichev, 31 January 1993 (Box 4)
      Use copy reference number: 94039_a_0006675
    - Khrunichev, 31 January 1993 (Box 4)
      Use copy reference number: 94039_a_0008786
    - Konstantinov, Il'ia (Box 4)
      Use copy reference number: 94039_a_0008329
    - Krasnitskiĭ, 14 July 1995 (Box 4)
      Use copy reference number: 94039_a_0008879
    - Krestianinov, Evgeniĭ, 1995 July 20 (Box 4)
    - Kriuchkov, Anatoliĭ (Box 4)
      Use copy reference number: 94039_a_0006679
    - Kulik, Gennadiĭ, 17 July 1995 (Box 4)
      Use copy reference number: 94039_a_0008880
    - Kuptsov, Valentin, 28 July 1995 (Box 4)
      Use copy reference number: 94039_a_0008883
    - Kurginian, Sergeĭ, 19 May 1995 (Box 4)
      Use copy reference number: 94039_a_0008884
    - Kuz'min, Alekseĭ (Box 4)
      Use copy reference number: 94039_a_0008885
    - Mashinostroenie and Impuls sound recordings (Box 4)
      Use copy reference number: 94039_a_0006669
      Part 1: Machinostwewie part 1
      Part 2: Machinostwewie part 2
      Part 3: Machinostwewie part 3
      Part 4: Impuls part 3
    - Mau, Vladimir, 02 August 1995 (Box 4)
      Use copy reference number: 94039_a_0008288
    - Mekhanik, Alexander, Chairman of the Executive Committee for the Republican Party of Russia, 14 June 1995 (Box 4)
      Use copy reference number: 94039_a_0008887
    - Mekhanik, Alexander, Chairman of the Executive Committee for the Republican Party of Russia, 03 August 1994 (Box 4)
      Use copy reference number: 94039_a_0008888
    - Minzhurenko, Aleksandr, 12 May 1995 (Box 4)
      Use copy reference number: 94039_a_0006681
    - Mironov, Boris S. (Box 4)
      Use copy reference number: 94039_a_0008328
    - Mitrofanov, Alekseĭ, 16 June 1995 (Box 4)
      Use copy reference number: 94039_a_0008889
    - Mitrokhin, Sergeĭ (Box 4)
      Use copy reference number: 94039_a_0008890
    - Mitrokhin, Sergeĭ, 29 May 1995 (Box 4)
      Use copy reference number: 94039_a_0008892
    - Osovtsov, Aleksandr, 21 July 1995 (Box 5)
      Use copy reference number: 94039_a_0008906
    - Ponomarev, Lev, 1995 July 9 (Box 5)
    - Privatization, 30 November 1992 (Box 5)
      Use copy reference number: 94039_a_0008897
    - Privatization, 03 December 1992 (Box 5)
      Use copy reference number: 94039_a_0008898
    - Privatization, 12 April 1992 (Box 5)
      Use copy reference number: 94039_a_0008901
    - Privatization round table panel discussion (Box 5)
      Use copy reference number: 94039_a_0006659
      This panel discussion concerns private enterprises, state-owned enterprises, and the privatization of state-owned enterprises.
      The moderator conducts the discussion in English, and the Russian(?) speakers' statements are translated into English.
      It sounds like this discussion took place in the San Francisco Bay Area, but not at Stanford University.
    - Privatization roundtable, 29 November 1992 (Box 5)
      Use copy reference number: 94039_a_0008902
      Bunkin
      Grigoriev
      Vorotnikov
      Baxap
      Turin
    - Rumiantsev, Oleg, 29 May 1995 (Box 5)
      Use copy reference number: 94039_a_0008908
    - SDPR (Sotsial-demokraticheskaia partiia Rossii), press conference, 02 February 1991 (Box 5)
      Use copy reference number: 94039_a_0008909
    - SDPR (Sotsial-demokraticheskaia partiia Rossii), press conference, 29 October 1990 (Box 5)
      Use copy reference number: 94039_a_0009089
    - Shabad, Anatoliĭ, 04 July 1995 (Box 5)
      Use copy reference number: 94039_a_0009080
    - Sheĭnis, Viktor, 12 May 1995 (Box 5)
      Use copy reference number: 94039_a_0009081
    - Sheĭnis, Viktor, 21 August 1995 (Box 5)
      Use copy reference number: 94039_a_0009083
    - Sheĭnis, Viktor, 10 October 1997 (Box 5)
      The accessioned cassette is effectively blank.
    - Shelesh, Petr, 1995 July 20 (Box 5)
      The accessioned cassette is effectively blank, like the tape machine during the interview was on, but the microphone wasn't plugged in.
    - Slavin, B., 23 June 1995 (Box 5)
      Use copy reference number: 94039_a_0009088
    - Stankevich, Sergeĭ, 1995 July 21 (Box 5)
    - "Sticky Fingers," copies of commercial albums, undated (Box 5)
    - 'Svetlana,' NPO (nauchno-proizvodstvennoe ob"edinenie) (Box 5)
      Use copy reference number: 94039_a_0006673
    - 'Svetlana,' NPO (nauchno-proizvodstvennoe ob"edinenie), 30 September 1992-12 October 1992 (Box 5)